INDIAN TUTOR | FOUR-POSE WEBRTC SHOWCASE
2-FRAME CROSSFADE | 100 MS AT 20 FPS
SILENT | NEUTRAL RESTING
SILENT | ACTIVE LISTENING / EMPATHETIC
BLEND: NEUTRAL > LISTENER
SILENT | NEUTRAL RESTING
BLEND: LISTENER > NEUTRAL
SILENT | SPEAKING DIRECT (NO AUDIO)
BLEND: NEUTRAL > SPEAKING
SILENT | NEUTRAL RESTING
BLEND: SPEAKING > NEUTRAL
SILENT | LIGHT SMILE
BLEND: NEUTRAL > SMILE
SILENT | ACTIVE LISTENING / EMPATHETIC
BLEND: SMILE > LISTENER
SILENT | SPEAKING DIRECT (NO AUDIO)
BLEND: LISTENER > SPEAKING
SILENT | ACTIVE LISTENING / EMPATHETIC
BLEND: SPEAKING > LISTENER
SILENT | LIGHT SMILE
BLEND: LISTENER > SMILE
SILENT | SPEAKING DIRECT (NO AUDIO)
BLEND: SMILE > SPEAKING
SILENT | LIGHT SMILE
BLEND: SPEAKING > SMILE
SILENT | NEUTRAL RESTING
BLEND: SMILE > NEUTRAL
TTS | EMPATHY REACTION
TTS | SPEAKING DIRECT
BLEND: EMPATHY > SPEAKING
TTS | NEUTRAL RETURN
BLEND: SPEAKING > NEUTRAL
SILENT | NEUTRAL RESTING
TTS | LIGHT SMILE REACTION
TTS | SPEAKING DIRECT
BLEND: SMILE > SPEAKING
TTS | NEUTRAL RETURN
BLEND: SPEAKING > NEUTRAL